Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 8: Boxes 443-506
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 8: Boxes 443-506
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 456, Folder 7)
  - Item 13: 1972 One-day Legislative Conference, Publication (Box 456, Folder 7)
  - Item 14: Voting Records of New York US Senators & Representatives, 1965-1966 (Box 456, Folder 7)
  - Item 15: Legislative Bulletin from the State AFL, 1961; Publication (Box 456, Folder 7)
  - Item 16: 1972 NYS Legislature and Standing Committees with alaphabetical index, Publication (Box 456, Folder 7)
  - Item 17: NYS Legislature 1966, Publication (Box 456, Folder 7)
  - Item 18: Official AFL-CIO COPE voting records of NY, 1971-1972 (Box 456, Folder 7)
  - Item 19: State Senate and Assembly. voting record, 1960-1962 (Box 456, Folder 7)
  - Item 20: 1971 New York State Legislaturewith alphabetical index, Publication (Box 456, Folder 7)
  - Item 21: Labor's positive legislative program, 1962; Publication (Box 456, Folder 7)
  - Item 22: 1966, 1970 Recommendations for endorsement for the NYS Legislature (Box 456, Folder 7)
  - Item 23: 1966 Recommendations on Statewide proposition and amendments, Publication (Box 456, Folder 7)
  - Item 24: New York State AFL-CIO Resolutions 1 through 102, 1971; Publication (Box 456, Folder 7)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 456, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: COPE Newsletter, 1962; Publication (Box 456, Folder 8)
    Notes: Jan.-Feb. (1962)
  - Item 2: COPE Newsletter, 1963; Publication (Box 456, Folder 8)
    Notes: May, Dec. (1963)
  - Item 3: COPE Newsletter, 1964; Publication (Box 456, Folder 8)
    Notes: Jan.-Feb., Apr.-May, Aug. (1964)
  - Item 4: COPE Newsletter, 1965; Publication (Box 456, Folder 8)
    Notes: Jan.-Dec. (1965)
  - Item 5: COPE Newsletter, 1966; Publication (Box 456, Folder 8)
    Notes: Jan., Mar.-Sept. (1966)
  - Item 6: COPE Newsletter, 1967; Publication (Box 456, Folder 8)
    Notes: Jan.-Dec. (1967)
  - Item 7: COPE Newsletter, 1968; Publication (Box 456, Folder 8)
    Notes: Jan.-Apr., Aug.-Oct., Dec. (1968)
  - Item 8: COPE Newsletter, 1969; Publication (Box 456, Folder 8)
    Notes: Jan.-Oct. (1969)
  - Item 9: COPE Newsletter, 1970; Publication (Box 456, Folder 8)
    Notes: Jan.-May, July-Aug. (1970)
  - Item 10: COPE Newsletter, 1971; Publication (Box 456, Folder 8)
    Notes: Jan.-Mar., June-July, Oct.-Dec. (1971)
  - Item 11: COPE Newsletter, 1972; Publication (Box 456, Folder 8)
    Notes: Feb.-Mar. (1972)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 457, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Legislative News, 1959-1960 (Box 457, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.1:no.1-3, 3(supplement), 4 (1959-1960)
  - Item 2: Legislative News, 1961; Publication (Box 457, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2:no.1-2, 4-5 (1961)
  - Item 3: Legislative News, 1962; Publication (Box 457, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.3:no.1-5 (1962)
  - Item 4: Legislative News, 1960; Publication (Box 457, Folder 1)
    Notes: Action Bulletin (Feb.-Apr., 1960)
  - Item 5: Legislative News, 1960; Publication (Box 457, Folder 1)
    Notes: Special Bulletin (May, 1960)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 457, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Spirit of '76 (a proposed plan of Political Action for consideration by the 18th Constitutional Convention of the New York State AFL-CIO..), 1976; Publication (Box 457, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Legislative Conference ---Agenda, 1973; Publication (Box 457, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: 1973 One-day Legislative Conference, Publication (Box 457, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Legislative Report, 1964; Publication (Box 457, Folder 2)
    Notes: Jan. 31, 1964
  - Item 5: Legislative Report, 1967; Publication (Box 457, Folder 2)
    Notes: Apr. 11, 1967, 1974
  - Item 6: Legislative Report, 1972; Publication (Box 457, Folder 2)
    Notes: June 7, 1972, Apr. 21, 1972, Feb. 28, 1972, Apr. 14, 1972
  - Item 7: Legislative Report, 1974; Publication (Box 457, Folder 2)
    Notes: 1974
  - Item 8: Legislative Program, 1974-1975 (Box 457, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Legislature, 1973; Publication (Box 457, Folder 2)
    Notes: With alphabetical index
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Bill no. S.I. 2818, S.P. 3018, A.I. 3829, A.P. 3997, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Procedure for regularizing employment of Longshoremen, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Protects Policyholers during insurance agents' strike, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Collective bargaining for thruway concession workers, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Bill assures compliance with minimum wage and safety requirements by firms doing business with the state, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Bill assures compliance with minimum wage and safety requirements by firms doing business with the state, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
    Notes: c.2
  - Item 7: Bill gives representation on funeral directing advisory board to those employed in the trade, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: Industrial council should not be abolished, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: Employers' unjustified attempt to shirk responsibility under workmen's compensation, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: Four bills to improve liegislative procedures, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: Extension of compulsory school age to 18 years aids in reducing youth unemployment, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 12: Employment of children in the harvest of berries, fruits and vegetables, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 13: Repeal of regressive child labor provisions, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 14: Reqpportionment, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 15: Removal of election law literacy test requirement, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 16: Prohibit recruitment of professional strikebreakers, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 17: State minimum wage - $2.00 per hour, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 18: Time off to vote, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 19: Full labor relations rights for workers in non-profit hospitals, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 20: First class citizenship for employees of non-profit institutions, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 21: Manhole safety, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 22: First-aid stations required at hazardous jobs, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 23: Licensing of stationary engineers, hoisting and portable engineers and firemen, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 24: Provision of sanitary facilities at construction sites, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 25: Limitation on crane boom length, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 26: Safety nets required at construction sites, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 27: Elevator service required at construction sites over six stories, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 28: Prohibit use of explosive power tools in building construction work, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 29: Extending duration of disability benefits, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 30: Disability benefits - employee voice in choice of insurance carrier, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 31: Computation of disability benefits rate in same manner as workmen's compensation rate, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 32: Dependent's allowances included in disability benefits, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 33: Financing of disability benefits by employer contributions, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 34: Disability benefits during unemployment insurance suspension, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 35: Non-occupational disability benefits to cover hospitalization expenses, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 36: Automatic adjustment of maximum disability benefit rate, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 37: Computation of disability benefits, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 38: Workmen's compensation coverage for farm workers, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 39: Require attendants in multiple dwelling, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 40: Prevents discrimination against employees of non-profit organizations working in buildings operated for profit, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 41: Improved minimum wage necessary in fight against poverty, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 42: Interference with collective bargaining agreement, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 43: Disability benefits cut, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 44: Arbitrary denial of unemployment insurance benefits, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 45: Regressive measure weakens child labor safeguards, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 46: Bill lessens workmen's compensation protection for workers exposed to radiation, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 47: Proposal weakens unemployment insurance fund, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 48: Unwarranted interference with state insurance fund, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 49: Harmful restriction of legal advertising, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 50: Bill to curtail hospital construction severely restricts employment opportunities, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 51: Collective bargaining strengthened, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 52: Interferes with collective bargaining negotiations, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 53: Fair regulation of outdoor advertising, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 54: This bill would provide that any exposure to hazards of radiation after, 1964; Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 55: Bill upsets court decision in unemployment insurance prevailing wage determinations, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 56: Elimination of discrimination in government contracts, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 57: Bill removes safeguards in employment of children, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 58: Unemployment insurance coverage for domestic workers, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 59: Employers' back door attempt to shirk responsibility under workmen's compensation, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 60: Beneficial extension of health center services, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 61: To provide blinded worker with 'seeing-eye' dog, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 62: Restricts legitimate practice of hypnosis, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 63: Unrestricted power to superintendent of public works jeopardizes all jobs in outdoor advertising fields, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 64: Unfair increase in employment agency fee, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 65: New system of probationary drivers' licenses recognizes modern traffic conditions, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 66: Special interest bill weakens labor laws, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 67: Bill threatens basic concept of workmen's compensation, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 68: Licensing placement employees gives protection to public, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 69: Further study needed on complex disability benefits proposal, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 70: This bill provides that the limit of liability under the motor vehicle accident indemnification corporation, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 71: Salary increase for workmen's compensation referees, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 72: Unfair limitation on right to workmen's compensation, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 73: Side mirrors on buses, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 74: Prohibition of corporate practice of optometry is not in the public interest, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 75: Protection for job applicants, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 76: Bill reduces protections in service of income executions, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 77: Save workmen's compensation from the courts, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 78: Bill harmful to public health and interests of union members employed in the optical trades, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 79: Bill extends time to request hearings on employment insurance claims, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 80: Against the repeal of full crew laws, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 81: Bill harmful to rights of injured workers, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 82: Reduces unemployment insurance benefits for fully qualified claimants, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 83: The 'Fair Trade' Act by any other name smells just as bad., Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 84: Restricts free choice of workmen's compensation doctor, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 85: Bill seeks to limit labor relations contracts, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 86: Prohibit requirement of lie detector test as a condition of employment, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 87: Bill provides penalties for employers paying less than prevailing wage, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 88: Safeguards weakened on factory work for women, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 89: Bill unfair to public employees in prevailing wage proceedings, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 90: Sets fair standards for disciplinary hearings, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 91: Lowering of standards of responsibility for physicians and surgeons is dangerous to public health, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 92: Administrative expenses of the state insurance fund, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 93: Provision of free textbooks for secondary school pupils, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 94: Bill aims to restrict state insurance fund operations, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 95: Would ban merging of paid fire-police dept, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 96: Removes protection for employees in wage assignments, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 97: Single wage complaint to cover similar claims, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 98: Safety standards for coin-operated manufacturing machines, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 99: Improper practices act prosecutions in Albany unfair to defendant, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 100: Threat to workmen's compensation and federal disability benefits programs, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 101: Compensate claimants for time lost at workmen's compensation hearings and medical examinations, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 102: Workmen's compensation - replacement of damaged eyeglasses, false teeth and artificial eyes, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 103: Workmen's compensation benefits for permanent loss of use of an eye, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 104: Workmen's compensation - supplementation of obsolete benefit rates for permanently disabled workers, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 105: Workmen's compensation - arbitrary time limit removed on claims for silicosis and other dust diseases, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 106: Workmen's compensation benefits for partial disability due to silicosis or other dust diseases, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 107: Workmen's compensation - determination of wage earning capacity in cases of partial disability, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 108: Workmen's compensation awards for temporary total disability in connection with permanent partial disability, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 109: Occupational aggravation of pre-existing injuries, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 110: Dependents' allowances in workmen's compensation benefits, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 111: Workmen's compensation benefits. reduction of waiting period, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 112: Workmen's compensation widows benefits, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 113: Over the counter method of unemployment insurance benefit payment, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 114: Automatic adjustment of maximum rate for workmen's compensation benefits, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 115: Elimination of double disqualifications for unemployment insurance benefits resulting from the same act, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 116: Revision of eligibility requirement for unemployment insurance benefits, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 117: Unemployment insurance waiting period eliminated, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 118: Removal of suspension of unemployment insurance benefits for non-participants in industrial disputes, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 119: Unemployment insurance benefit disqualifications, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 120: Thorough review urged of unemployment insurance experience rating provisions, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 121: Repeals restiction on unemployment insurance benefits during vacations and holidays, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 122: Repeal of unemployment insurance pension-offset provision, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 123: Unemployment insurance coverage for agricultural workers, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 124: Extension of unemployment insurance benefits to employees of non-profit institutions and local governments, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 125: Extension o funemployment insurance coverage to domestic workers, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 126: Requiring employers to post deposit on request for hearing under the unemployment insurance law, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 127: Repeal of experience rating provisions for employer unemployment insurance contributions, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 128: Dependency benefits under the unemployment insurance law, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 129: Extension of unemployment insurance benefit duration to 39 weeks, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 130: Repeal of the Condon-Wadlin Law, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 131: Unemployment insurance: computation of average weekly wage, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 132: Unemployment insurance maximum benefit rate adjusted automatically, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 133: Apprentice training proposal, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 134: 1970 One-day Legislative Conference, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 135: Honest textile label requirements, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 136: Reduction in standard work week to 35 hours, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 137: Honest labeling of passenger ship services, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 138: Protects employees from loss of earned vacation pay, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 139: Abolition of waterfront commission, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 140: Preference for New York bidders aids business, labor, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
  - Item 141: Increase in unemployment insurance tax base, Publication (Box 457, Folder 3)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 457, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Resolution No. 61. Endorsement of the Kennedy-Johnson Ticket, 1960; Publication (Box 457, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Industrial Bulletin, 1964; Publication (Box 457, Folder 4)
    Notes: Sept. 1964.
  - Item 3: The Thruway Motel is non-union, Publication (Box 457, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: 35th Annual Convention report of Officers, 1962; Publication (Box 457, Folder 4)
    Author: Union Label and Service Trades Dept. of the State of New York
  - Item 5: A lively New York Radio program gives many insights into labor-management relations, 1960; Publication (Box 457, Folder 4)
    Author: Austin H. Perlow
    Notes: Article
  - Item 6: Announces a community public relations project, 1961; Publication (Box 457, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: correspondence - We would like to keep you abreast of the latest efforts of our Dept., Publication (Box 457, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: Constitution and by-laws. (serial), 1961; Publication (Box 457, Folder 4)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 457, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: buyers' guide official directory, 1961; Publication (Box 457, Folder 5)
    Notes: 5th ed.
  - Item 2: buyers' guide official directory, 1963; Publication (Box 457, Folder 5)
    Notes: 6th ed.
  - Item 3: buyers' guide official directory, 1966; Publication (Box 457, Folder 5)
    Notes: 7th ed.
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 457, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: buyers' guide official directory, 1975; Publication (Box 457, Folder 6)
    Notes: 1975 ed.
  - Item 2: buyers' guide official directory, 1976; Publication (Box 457, Folder 6)
    Notes: bicentennial ed.
- Union Label and Service Trades Dept. of the State of New York, Publication (Box 457, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: NEWS, 1961; Publication (Box 457, Folder 7)
    Notes: Feb. (1961), v.2:no.9 (1961)
  - Item 2: NEWS, 1962; Publication (Box 457, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.3:no. 1, 3 (1962)
  - Item 3: NEWS, 1965; Publication (Box 457, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.7 (1965)
  - Item 4: NEWS, 1966; Publication (Box 457, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.8 (1966)
  - Item 5: NEWS, 1976; Publication (Box 457, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.49 (1976)
  - Item 6: NEWS, 1980; Publication (Box 457, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.53 (1980)
  - Item 7: NEWS, 1981; Publication (Box 457, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.54 (1981)
  - Item 8: Press Release. Syracuse named for NY label trades 9th Empire State Labor-Management Show, Publication (Box 457, Folder 7)
    Notes: Press release
  - Item 9: Union Label Trades News and Directory, 1947; Publication (Box 457, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.1:no.8 (1947)
  - Item 10: 33rd Annual Convention of the Union, 1960; Publication (Box 457, Folder 7)
  - Item 11: Year-Round consumer education program launched by 32nd Annual convention, 1959; Publication (Box 457, Folder 7)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 457, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Legislative Bulletin. 1-6, 1959; Publication (Box 457, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: COPE Newsletter, 1963; Publication (Box 457, Folder 8)
    Notes: Jan.-Nov. (1963)
  - Item 3: COPE Newsletter, 1964; Publication (Box 457, Folder 8)
    Notes: Jan.-May, Aug., Nov.-Dec. (1964)
  - Item 4: NEWS, 1963; Publication (Box 457, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.4:no.1-2, 10-11 (1963)
  - Item 5: NEWS, 1964; Publication (Box 457, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.5:no.1-15, 18-19 (1964)
  - Item 6: NEWS, 1965; Publication (Box 457, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.6:no.1-2 (1965)
  - Item 7: NEWS, 1971; Publication (Box 457, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.12:no.1 (1971)
  - Item 8: News from. Meany, Corgett, Rockefeller set to address State AFL-CIO Convention at Kiamesha Lake, 1963; Publication (Box 457, Folder 8)
  - Item 9: Report by Louis Hollander3rd Constituional convention, 1960; Publication (Box 457, Folder 8)
  - Item 10: Workmen's compensation enters its fortieth year in New York State, 1953; Publication (Box 457, Folder 8)
    Author: Mary Donlon
    Notes: Address delivered at the 90th Annual Convention, New York State Federation of Labor
  - Item 11: Supplement to Report on Legislation. legislative voting records Senate Assembly. Final calenday of 1959 Program bills, Publication (Box 457, Folder 8)
- AFL-CIO (American Federation of Labor - Congress of Industrial Organizations)., Publication (Box 458, Folder 1)